uwhealth.org 2018-10-01

# Website Privacy Policy | UW Health | Madison, WI

Welcome to UW Health’s website (“Site”). The privacy of your information is important to us. This privacy policy describes our privacy practices in connection with information we collect through the Site. It does not apply to information obtained from other sources such as information received via the mail. Terms such as “we”, “our” or “us” refer to UW Health, which includes the University of Wisconsin Hospitals and Clinics Authority, the University of Wisconsin Medical Foundation, Inc. and affiliated entities.

_Personally Identifiable Information_

We may collect and use personal information that identifies you that you voluntarily give us if you use the Site. The personal information may include your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, date of birth, age, gender, financial and payment information and any other information you choose to provide to us. We will use the personal information we collect for the purposes for which you provided it (to register for classes or programs, purchase memberships and obtain other services), to contact you regarding programs or services, process payments, provide information we believe may be of interest to you, manage programs and services and to improve your experience as a user of our programs and services and the Site. We may use your personally identifiable information to review the status or activity of users. We may aggregate information to better understand how users use our services and to improve services or the Site.

We may use your personally identifiable information if we believe the law requires it, to comply with legal process such as a court order or other process. We may use third party suppliers or service providers to help us collect, process, maintain and analyze this personally identifiable information. We may also use third party suppliers to host the Site and gather and use information for the purposes for which you provided it to us. However, we require such services providers to maintain the confidentiality of the information. We do not sell names or other personally identifiable information. You can choose whether to provide personally identifiable information, but you may not be able to use the Site if you do not provide it.

_Non-Personally Identifiable Information_

When you visit the Site, we (or a third party vendor or contractor on our behalf) may passively collect non-personally identifiable information about you, such as the following: 

  * Internet protocol (IP) address for your computer/device
  * Internet service provider
  * Website from which you arrived
  * Operating system and web browser software
  * Date and time of your visit
  * Pages you visit on this Site
  * Terms you use in our Site’s search engines 

We use cookies (small text files that collect information about website activity) and web beacons (small image files that monitor web activity). The use of cookies and web beacons can help us improve your enjoyment of this Site, for example, by remembering your address or other information when you request information or services on the Site and identifying the pages that are most popular. We also use the information we collect for Site analytics. You can disable cookies by changing preference settings in your web browser, but you may find that some functions require cookies.

Third-party tools like Google Analytics help website administrators track site usage, understand how users find sites, and improve website function and content.  Like many websites, we also use Google Analytics to collect information about your use of our Site. Google uses this information to provide us with reports about traffic to our Site and your visit to our Site.

We do not request, seek or intentionally collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Parents or legal guardians are responsible for determining the appropriate content for their children and to monitor access and use of the Site.

_Links_

The Site may contain links to other websites, which may have different privacy practices and policies. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of any third party website. You should review the privacy policy of every website before using the website or providing information.

We may change this privacy policy from time to time without prior notice to you. If we change this privacy policy, a new privacy policy that reflects the changes will be posted, with the date it was updated. Please check this page periodically for changes.

If you use this Site, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy and UW Health’s Terms and Conditions, which are on [uwhealth.org](https://www.uwhealth.org/) and incorporated into this Site. Click [here](https://www.uwhealth.org/about-uwhealth/terms-and-conditions/11421) to see the Terms and Conditions. By using this Site, you assume full responsibility for use of any information by UW Health.

The information on this Site is not intended as a substitute for professional medical advice or care. You should consult with your health care provider with questions regarding any new exercise program or services on you and your treatment plan. 

Last Updated: March 24, 2017
